Nathan Gusky

Denver, CO | (850) 556-3452 | Nathangusky13@gmail.com | Github | LinkedIn

Software Engineer

Full-stack web developer with experience in React and Ruby, with a background in hospitality, physical therapy, and architecture. Having a diverse and comprehensive background I can tackle multiple projects with varying challenges and problem solve with attention to detail. From managing a 20-person serving team to listening to the needs of people and adjusting a regime to suit their needs, I can be an asset to any team of any size.

Technical skills

Ruby | Rails | HTML | JavaScript | SQL | React | Firebase | ES6/7 | Mongoose | GraphQL | NextJS | Sanity | Tailwind CSS

Technical Projects

Portfolio Website - Github

Personal portfolio website to display quick and easy access of my personal information and previous projects

- Axios used to email contact information
- Sanity.io for the backend to display all necessary information

Droneography – Github

Social site to display photos taken by drone pilots and to communicate with other pilots.

- Authenticated users with google login
- Sanity backend for users to store data
- Designed with tailwind css

Professional Experience

Crowdcoursing May - Present

Frontend Developer

- Linking process of payments using swipe is
- Designing and developing the UI/UX

Il Fornaio, DTC, CO 2018 – 2020

Manager

- Managed 20+ servers on the floor on a daily basis to provide a hospitable environment for guests
- Promptly greet guests and assist servers with parties of 30 plus

Ambli Gourmet Eatery and Wine, Denver, CO

Sep 2015 – 2018

2016 - 2019

Server | Bartender

- Proven ability to detail menu items to guests in a manor to increase sales in a polite and inviting tactic
- Opened a new building and trained staff to improve techniques and knowledge

Denver Health, Denver Co

Physical Therapy Aide

• Helped assist PT's when patients needed an extra hand and assistance

Education

Flatiron School, Denver, CO 2020 - 2021

Full-stack web development

University of Colorado Denver, Denver, CO

- BA in Biology for Physical Therapy
 - o Graduated with a 3.5

Florida Agriculture and Mechanical University, Tallahassee, FL

- Coursework completed for Bachelor of Arts in Architecture
 - Knowledge of Autodesk products